I love young women! Let me gobble them up!
In that case, just go see a prostitute.
Thank you for protecting me.
You're welcome.
Huh.
Your palms are sweaty. Gross.
That said, I might look good in a flower garden like this,
but not a fatty like you.
Don't overdo it.
More haste, less speed.
Thank you.
Come again.
Come on, Ura-Acca, say something too.
A-Are you okay?!
Where does it hurt?
M-My ribs hurt.
I think they're broken.
A doctor should—
They never told me my body here would get hurt!
I'm terribly sorry, but that's none of our concern.
That's your responsibility.
You're awful!
Get used to it.
Adults suck, even in this place.
Huh?
Oh, I'm fine now.
I'm Kawai Rika.
Like "kawaii," 'cause I'm so cute.
Are you saving a friend, too?
Are those color contacts?
Huh?
Cool idea, mixing colors.
That might go viral.
No.
It's...
Does it bother you? Sorry.
Anyway, I forgot my wallet.
Sorry, but could you spot me cash?
Huh?
They didn't tell me the second one would cost money.
I most certainly did.
It'd be a pain to go back for my wallet.
Please! I'll pay you back!
Uh, umm...
Y-Yeah, okay, sure.
She will, huh?
Here.
Thanks.
Huh?
Come see me again, okay?
Just kidding!
A handshake event?
Rika?
How'd you know where I live?
Ai-kyun, Ai-Ai, A-chan, Ai-ty, Aijorina.
What do people call you?
"Ohto."
I don't really have a nickname.
Oh... so that's how it is, huh?
I followed you yesterday.
Oh, to pay me back for—
Sorry! I forgot my wallet again.
You know someone in here?
Yeah. Her name's Neiru.
So, Neiru's nailed down in bed?
Don't rush your rehabilitation.
I'm fine.
You have to give your body time to rest,
or you'll only make things worse.
Don't worry, doctor.
We're still young.
Don't put too much confidence in youth.
I guess I shouldn't.
I'll be careful.
Thank you!
Thank you.
Oh, yeah.
Don't overdo it with this.
Yes, I know.
Thank you.
This is Kawai Rika.
I met her buying Eggs.
I see.
Remember it as Kawaii Rika, since I'm so super cute.
I won't.
A tsundere, huh?
Want to form a unit with me?
I used to be a junior idol.
A group called All-Out Kiss. Ever heard of us?
Never.
We broke up.
All the others were too ugly.
Come on. The two of us might get popular.
Not interested.
That's too bad.
I love kiwi.
What about me?
You've got nice legs.
Wanna be a backup dancer?
Backup?
Ai?
Oh?
Welcome!
A friend?
I'm Kawai Rika.
Like "kawaii," because I'm so cute.
H-Hey.
Welcome home. A friend of yours?
I'll leave for today, since I see you have company.
Oh yes, all right.
I'm sorry, Mr. Sawaki.
Don't be. It's no trouble.
Thank you for always coming by.
You've got one good-looking daddy.
He's not my dad.
Please, come in.
I'll bring you some roll cake later.
Your school counselor? Whoa.
Hang on, you're a shut-in?
Yeah. Since this semester started.
Oh, so you're out for attention.
What?
You're trying to get your hot
counselor to worry about you, right?
N-No, I'm not!
It's because Koito died.
Koito?
Yeah. She was my only friend.
Quit it with the depressing talk.
It'll spoil the cake.
Aren't you trying to save your friend—
She's not my friend.
She's my fan.
My little wallet who'd buy me anything.
Your "wallet"?
My daddy says a beautiful woman doesn't need a wallet.
Someone will always offer to pay for her.
Of course, he got divorced.
Oh, I'll pay you back for the Egg.
Promise.
Coming!
Wow, it looks delicious!
Oh, I buy these roll cakes all the time.
You'd better.
I've been short on cash since Chiemi died.
So, I'm gonna save her and get my wallet back.
Chiemi's ugly and a real fatty.
She has gross, sweaty palms, too.
Way too embarrassing to call a friend, right?
You pick your friends based on looks?
Yup.
You gonna eat that?
Come on.
It's mine.
Was that Koito girl cute?
Yeah.
More "pretty" than "cute."
Compared to Neiru?
Neiru is cool, but Koito was more gentle and soft.
She was graceful and innocent, I guess.
See? It was looks.
No!
Ugh.
S-Sorry.
That's cold.
I'll grab a towel.
Ai, lend me some pajamas!
Did you call your parents?
Who cares about her?
Scratch the surface, and she's all slimy.
Everyone is.
Long baths will give you dry skin.
I won't cut anymore. I promised.
Koito, is club...
Ai?
Ohto?
Excuse me!
Why, Koito?
Was it because of Mr. Sawaki?
I knew it. You don't look too good in a flower garden either.
Look, that's my little wallet Chiemi over there.
She looks a little thinner from over here.
Why?
You synchronized.
We what?
You fell asleep near each other
and at almost the same time, so...
We synchronized.
But why aren't we in my dream?
You're pulled by whoever's feelings are stronger.
That can't be it!
She calls her friend her "wallet"!
How could—
Hey!
Crack them on "go"?
Ready, go.
Miko!
Mako!
Friends?
You're here! You're here!
I got to see you again!
We're huge fans of Yu-Yu.
We went to meet-ups and concerts and things.
Who's Yu-Yu?
A singer who committed suicide.
We're huge Yu-Yu fans.
So, we followed Yu-Yu and died as fast as we could.
Just like that?
It's not easy or casual.
That's basically the way fanatical fans are.
So, for now, we just have to...
Keep these girls safe until sunset.
I don't see any Seeno Evils.
The bystanders?
They're here. There's a swimming beach down below.
What are those?! They're adorbs!
Lucky. I wish we could swap.
That way!
I know!
Watch out!
What the hell?!
S-Sorry.
But it's your fault for standing there.
I told you to go that way!
Jeez!
Oh, what is it now?!
Take that!
Behind you!
Piece of cake.
Are you okay?!
I'm fine.
Go get 'em!
It could be hard to fight in the open.
Hmm...
Oh.
Your cuts aren't healing.
Oh, don't worry. These are old.
Just a youthful whatever.
Okay, show's over.
Tell me about Chiemi for real.
It's none of your business.
Yes, it is.
Handshake events for unpopular idols are surreal.
Just a few people lining up over and over.
Chiemi was a real idiot.
She got in line for me dozens, maybe hundreds of times.
She just gave me all her allowance
and New Year's money with a smile.
I believed I had a rich patron.
Then one day, I saw her shoplifting in town.
She'd been selling what she stole.
Oh, I totally know that feeling.
Yeah, we got sugar daddies for the same reason.
I didn't want that.
So, I told her I'd never be friends with a fan.
I said I'd be too embarrassed to be
seen with a fatty in the first place.
I said, "Never come back."
After that, another fan told me what happened.
Chiemi died.
She was skin and bones, like a mummy.
I couldn't forget her if I wanted to.
This...
This isn't Chiemi.
Run!
If it means I can see Chiemi again,
I'll kill as many as it takes!
Rika...
I understand.
There was a part of me that resented her.
We were friends, so why didn't she talk to me?
Why?!
If she'd asked me to die with her, like those girls did...
I'd...
I'd have...
Ai?!
Rika,
I'll kill them with you.
I wanted to die with her, too. To chase after Yu-Yu.
Wrapping people up?
Is this S&M?
This woman got arrested for stalking Yu-Yu!
Sachiko, the Asagaya Madame!
Sachiko...
You get them everywhere.
Delusional
weirdos who cross the line.
I can't see Yu-Yu because you're all so noisy.
It hurts. It hurts. It hurts!
Yu-Yu doesn't care about little
brats; Yu-Yu likes mature women!
Help!
Ai!
Who are you supposed to be?
We protect these girls.
From monsters.
You're promoted from backup dancer.
Little girls!
People won't fawn over you forever, you know!
No, we won't end up like you, lady.
Not in a million years.
Yeah.
Be quiet!
Rika, are you okay?
I... can't move.
Hey...
This might be bad.
Ai...
good luck.
No way...
Rika!
Rika?!
To be continued!